AYUSH RANJAN

Portfolio: https://ayushranjan15.github.io

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Data Analyst with experience in working on all stages of data science project cycle i.e. defining problems, cleaning data, selecting comparison matrix for models, testing different model and presenting insights to stakeholders. An inquisitive and collaborative nature with a lucid approach towards problems.

PROJECTS/PUBLICATIONS

Ames House Price prediction

Kaggle competion kernal

Trained and compared different regression models to find with lowest error EDA

Feature Engineering

Star Wars Data Cleaning

Cleaned and combined several tables using pandas library in Python

Is COVID - 19 Racist

Data Journalism

Combined and Cleaned data from public data sources Used pandas and matplotlib to explore a story on how COVID-19 is effecting minorities

EXPERIENCE

Analytics Consultant - Redwood Algorithms

June 2018 to August 2018

Defining problem statement as described by stakeholders

Gathering and cleaning data

Testing models

Communicating results

Intern - Dia capital advisory

February 2018 to May 2018

Maintain Database

Operations

EDUCATION

Masters of Data Science

RMIT University

2019 - Present

Bachelors of Technology - Electronics & Communication Manipal University Jaipur

2014-2018

Melbourne, VIC 0402484302 ayushranjan15@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayush-ranjan-5 https://github.com/AyushRanjan15

Skills

R
Python
Pandas
NumPy
Data Visualization
Data Cleaning
Command Line
Git and Version Control
SQL
APIs
Probability/Statistics
Data Journalism
Tensor Flow